字幕转制｜天外生物
感谢原字幕制作者
阴风阵阵
苏西邦妮决定在欧洲最著名的
Suzy Bannion decided to perfect her ballet studies...
舞蹈学校里精进她的芭蕾舞学习
In the most famous school of dance in Europe.
她选择了闻名遐迩的弗莱堡学院
She chose the celebrated academy of Freiburg.
这天早上九点，她离开纽约的肯尼迪机场
One day at 9:00 in the morning, She left Kennedy airport, New york,
并在当地时间晚上十点四十到达德国
And arrived in Germany at 10:40 p.m. Local time.
计程车！
Taxi!
计程车，计程车！
Taxi, taxi!
计程车！嘿，计程车！
Taxi! Hey, taxi!
计程车！计程车！
Taxi! Taxi!
你可以帮忙我吗？
Can you give me a hand?
Escherstrausse[德语]
Uh, Escherstrausse.
- 什么？ - Escherstrausse[德语]
- Was?  - Escherstrausse.
什么？
Was?
啊，Escherstrausse[德语]
Ah, Escherstrausse.
好，好
Ja, ja.
这场雨已经下很久了吗？
Has it been raining this hard for long?
下半小时了
Half an hour.
请你等我一分钟好吗？
Can you wait a minute, please?
- 哈罗？ - 是谁？
- Hello?  - Who is it?
苏西邦妮，我刚从纽约来的
Suzy Bannion. I just got in from New York.
- 我不认识你，走开！ - 但我有你们寄给我的信
- I don't know you. Go away!  - But I have the letter you sent.
听着，外面下这么大的雨，你让我进去，我会解释
Look, it's really raining hard. You could just let me in and I'll explain.
- 走开，走开！ - 但你不明白！
- Go away. Go away!  - But you don't understand!
等等！等一下，等等
Wait! Wait a minute. Wait.
哈罗，有人在那里吗？
Hello. Is anybody there?
哈罗？
Hello?
如果你喜欢沙发，你可以待到你高兴为止
If you're happy enough with the couch, you can stay for as long as you please.
谢谢，但我早上就会离开
Thanks, but I'll be leaving in the morning.
- 我会永远离开此地  - 喔，了不起，孩子
- I'm going away forever.  - Oh, big deal, kid.
你被学校退学了又怎么样？
So what if you've been thrown out of school?
我从幼稚园就老是被学校退学
I always got kicked out of school, beginning in kindergarten.
不，不是那样，我不在乎被退学
No, that's not it. I don't give a damn about getting kicked out.
那么呢？
Well, then?
跟你解释是没有用的
It's useless to try and explain it to you.
你不会了解的
You wouldn't understand.
所有事情似乎太…荒谬了
It all seems so...Absurd,
太难以置信了
So fantastic.
我所能做的就是尽快离开这里
All I can do is get away from here as soon as possible.
你介意我借用你的浴室吗？我想要把身体弄干
Would you mind if I used the bathroom? I'd like to dry off.
当然不介意，去吧
No, of course not. Go ahead.
嘿，你为什么不把它关上？
Hey, why don't you close it?
这样比较好，只是风而已
That's better. It was just the wind.
你看起来的确很糟
You sure are in bad shape.
你必须告诉我所有的事情
You have to tell me all about it.
风！窗户被吹开了
The wind! The windows burst open.
- 我吓到了  - 不，不是那个
- I got scared.  - No. That's not it.
我是说，什么事让你这么紧张？
I mean, what it is that's got you so upset.
好吧，你可以晚一点告诉我
Okay, you can tell me about it later.
让我进去！佩特！
Let me in! Pat!
佩特！佩特！
Pat! Pat!
帮帮我！帮帮我！这里发生了谋杀案！
Help me! Help me! There's a murderer!
帮帮我！帮帮忙！这里发生了谋杀案！
Help me! Help! There's a murderer!
帮帮我！帮帮忙！
Help me! Help!
不！不！不！
No! No! No!
帮帮我！
Help me!
帮帮忙！
Help!
这里发生了谋杀案！
There's a murderer!
不！
No!
- 早安  - 早安，丹尼尔
- Good morning.  - Good morning, Daniel.
早安，坦娜小姐
Good morning, miss Tanner.
- 早安，我能帮你什么吗？ - 是的，我是苏西邦妮
- Good morning. May I help you?  - Yes, I'm Suzy Bannion.
我们以为你昨天晚上会到，你在信上…
We expected you yesterday evening. You wrote us that...
对，我昨晚十点来到这里
Right. I did arrive last night about 10:00.
但是大门被锁起来，而且有人在对讲机里说…
But the door was locked, and somebody on the call box...
她不知道我是谁，所以不能让我进去
Said they didn't know who I was and couldn't let me in.
- 是谁这样对你说的？ - 我不知道，她没说她的名字
- Who said that to you?  - I don't know. She didn't say her name.
我很抱歉，但不管怎样，你来到我们这里了
I'm so sorry. At any rate, Now you're here among us,
欢迎来到我们的学院，我是坦娜小姐，这所学院的老师
So welcome to our academy. I'm miss Tanner, one of the instructors.
很高兴认识你
Nice to meet you.
请跟我来，我来跟你介绍布兰克夫人
Come along. I'd like to introduce you to madame Blanc,
我们的副校长
Our vice directress.
她是著名的芭蕾舞者
She was a very famous ballerina.
- 布兰克夫人  - 什么事？
- Madame Blanc?  - Yes?
苏西邦妮，我们的新学生
Suzy Bannion, our new student.
喔，是的
Oh, yes.
- 失陪了，先生们  - 好的，夫人
- Excuse me, gentlemen.  - Of course, madame.
你很漂亮，的确非常漂亮，他们是警察
You're pretty. Very pretty indeed. They're policemen.
我几年前在纽约认识一位邦妮女士，卡洛·邦妮
I knew a woman called Bannion years ago in New York. Carol Bannion.
- 她是我的阿姨  - 好极了！她是一位非凡的女人
- She's my aunt.  - Good! She's a marvelous woman,
她是我的朋友，赞助很多地方的艺术家
A friend and benefactress of artists everywhere.
我很高兴在这里教导她的侄女
I'm delighted to have her niece here.
我以我们学院女校长之名欢迎你的到来
Well, I offer our academy's official welcome in the name of our directress,
很遗憾她此刻不在学校
Who unfortunately is not here at the moment.
- 她目前在国外旅行  - 谢谢
- She's traveling abroad.  - Thank you.
艾伯特，请在楼上等我
Albert, please wait for me upstairs.
他是我的侄子，我非常喜欢他
He's my nephew. I'm very attached to him.
我必须尽快跟你说完…
I must tell you what I have to say very quickly...
因为那些先生正在等我
Because those gentlemen are waiting for me.
发生了一件非常可怕的事情
Something terrible, truly horrible, has happened.
我们的学生佩特·辛葛，昨天刚因为不当行为被退学
One of our students, Pat Hingle, who was expelled just yesterday for improper conduct,
然后昨晚被某个疯子杀了，这真是一件可怕的事
Was murdered last night by some madman. It's a frightening story.
不过我经常告诫我的学生，不是吗，坦娜小姐？
But I always warn our students, Don't I, miss Tanner?
我告诉她们要小心，不要交上不好的朋友
I tell them to be careful, not to get involved with questionable friendships.
我想跟你说，目前你的房间还没有空出来
What I wanted to tell you was that your room here isn't free yet.
- 只是一个小问题  - 是的，不过你不用担心
- Just a slight hitch.  - Yes, but don't worry.
我们为你在城里找到一个地方，和我们三年级的学生住在一起
We've found you a place to stay with one of our third-year students who lives in town.
你每个星期要付五十美元的房租
You'll have to pay 50 of your American dollars a week,
这是一个便宜的价钱，而且可以从你的学费中扣除
But it's a good price, and you can deduct it from your fee here.
现在我将你交给坦娜小姐照顾，她是我们这里资深的老师
Now I entrust you to the care of miss Tanner, one of our veteran teachers here.
她似乎有点严肃，但不要觉得不安，这只是她的作风，她对我也是这样的
Don't be upset if she seems a little stern or surly. It's only her manner. She's even that way with me.
她真的是一位优秀的老师
She really is an invaluable teacher.
- 跟我来  - 现在，先生们…
- Come with me.  - And now, gentlemen...
就如你所知，你必须修习三年
As you know, our courses last three years,
而且你要通过每学年末的考试
And you must pass an exam at the end of each year.
所以这名女孩是晚上大约十一点离开学校的吗？
So, the girl left the school About 11:00 in the evening?
- 据我所知是的  - 抱歉
- That's my information.  - Excuse me.
昨晚大约十一点我来到这里时，我看到一个女孩离开学校
When I got here last night about 11:00, I saw a girl leaving the school.
她是新学生，刚刚到达，她的外貌呢？
She's a new student. She just arrived. What did she look like?
她有一头金发和穿着一件棕色雨衣
Well, she had blonde hair and was wearing a brown raincoat.
- 她做了什么？ - 我不知道，我只在雨中看到她一会儿
- What did she do?  - I don't know. I only saw her for a minute in a storm.
那么你知道了吧？真的是十一点
So you see? It really was 11:00.
来吧？
Coming?
我们这里不教你怎么去跳舞，因为我们认为我们学生都已经知道了
We don't teach you how to dance here, because we presume our students already know how.
这是一所专门为培养专家而建立的学院
This is an established academy dedicated to specializing.
这是帕罗斯，我们学校的工友
This is Pavlos, our general handyman.
他很丑，不是吗？不用害怕这么说
He's really ugly, isn't he? don't be afraid to say so.
反正他听不懂你说什么，他只会罗马尼亚语
He can't understand you, anyway. He speaks only Romanian.
你看到他迷人的微笑吗？在他牙齿坏掉之前曾经非常的英俊
You see that gorgeous smile? He's been very handsome ever since he got those false teeth.
去年他发现自己有牙龈炎
Last year, he discovered He had gingivitis of the gums,
所以他拔掉所有的牙齿
So he had all his teeth pulled.
一天早上拔掉了上排牙齿，第二天，下排牙齿也都拔掉了
The top row one morning. The bottom row a day later.
砰！
Bang.
- 我们要去哪里？ - 去更衣室
- Where are we going?  - To the locker room.
我们学校也有一个游泳池，你可以在任何时间使用
We also have a swimming pool, which you can use when you want.
坦娜小姐，我有一些事要告诉你
Miss Tanner. I have something to tell you.
- 嘶嘎，嘶嘎，波丽鹦鹉  - 谁那样说的？闭嘴！
- Squawk, squawk. Polly parrot.  - Who said that? Shut up.
大家已经玩够这些游戏了吧
That's enough of these little games for the moment.
我向你们介绍我们的新同学，苏西·邦妮
I want to introduce Suzy Bannion, our new student.
你会找到几位也从美国来的女孩，例如米莉安
You'll find several fellow Americans among these girls...Miriam, for one.
- 你好  - 嗨，你的衣物柜在那里
- Hello.  - Hi. Your locker's over there.
除了舞鞋之外，柜子里什么都有
You'll find everything in there except shoes.
今天你可以先跟有两双舞鞋的人借
For today, you can borrow shoes from someone who has two pairs.
大家快一点，我会在红色房间等你们所有人
Hurry up, everybody. I'll be waiting for all of you in the red room.
跟我来吧
Come with me.
玛塔哈莉要去打小报告了
Mata Hari is going to file her report.
我的名字是欧嘉，你是我的房客
My name is Olga, and you're my tenant.
喔，嗨，很高兴认识你
Oh, hi. Nice to meet you.
她们跟我说，你每个星期要给我五十美元
They tell me you have to give me $50 a week.
- 没错  - 要预付
- Yeah.  - In advance.
不必担心，如果你认为我不…喔…
Well, don't worry. If you think I'm not...Oh...
不要生气，这里的人就是这样
Don't get hot under the collar. That's how people are here.
有人可以借我一双舞鞋吗？
Uh, can anybody lend me a pair of shoes?
- 我可以借你  - 喔，谢谢
- Yes. Me.  - Oh, thank you.
如果你想要买，我可以便宜卖给你，十五马克
If you want to buy them, I can make you a nice price. Fifteen marks.
谢谢，不用了，我行李里已经有一双了
Oh, no, thanks. I already have some in my suitcase.
我只要今天临时穿穿
I just need a pair for today.
但如果你不愿意…
But if you'd rather not...
不，没关系，拿去穿吧
No. Okay. Go ahead. Take them.
- 不过要记得还喔  - 当然
- But, uh, Give them back, hmm?  - Of course.
喔，对不起，我很抱歉
Oh, excuse me. I'm sorry.
没关系，这没什么
Oh, it's okay. It doesn't matter.
她们都在谈论钱，会不会让你很震惊？
Did they shake you up with all that talk about money?
我还不习惯这样
Well, I'm not exactly used to it.
跟我刚来时一样
Same with me at first.
后来我发现这是一种迷人的习惯
Then I found out it's a charming habit around here.
每当我念这些名字…
I once read that names...
这些开头是“S”字母的…
Which begin With the letter "S"...
是蛇的名字
Are the names of snakes.
明年我毕业后
Next year, after I finish the course,
我将到日内瓦国家芭蕾舞学校任教
I've got an offer from the state school of ballet in Geneva.
那你呢？
What about you?
我会回美国，但我还不确定要做什么
Well, I'll go back to yhe states, but I'm not exactly sure what I'll do.
谢谢，我的房间很漂亮
Hey, thanks. My room is really pretty.
- 喜欢吗？ - 喜欢
- Like it?  - Uh-huh.
那让我很高兴，我们一定会相处得很好，我觉得你很可爱
That makes me happy. I bet we'll do nicely together. I think you're sweet.
即使我有蛇的名字？
Even if I have the name of a snake?
我只是开玩笑
I was just kidding.
不要跟我说你像莎拉一样敏感
Don't tell me you're as touchy as Sara.
不会
No.
哈罗？
Hello?
喔，嗨！不，不，不
Oh, hi! No, no, no.
你做得很对
You did the right thing.
- 嗨  - 嗨
- Hi.  - Hi.
喔，你不用把这些东西搬过来
Oh, you didn't have to bring these over here.
我可以明天自己去拿
I could've picked them up myself tomorrow.
我还以为你可能会用到
I thought you might be needing them.
是的，但是真的不需要这么麻烦你
Yes, but it really wasn't necessary.
- 不管怎样，多谢  - 喔，没什么
- Anyway, thanks a lot.  - Oh, no. It's nothing.
- 再见  - 再见
- Ciao.  - Ciao.
- 你不想再多待一会儿吗？ - 不，谢了，我没时间了
- Don't you want to stay for a while?  - No, thanks. I can't.
我住在学校，得在半小时内赶回去吃晚餐
I live at the school, so I've got to be back for supper in half an hour.
- 我必须走了  - 待一会儿也不行吗？
- I have to.  - Just for a minute?
不，我真的要走了
No, no, really. I have to be going.
如果我太晚去吃晚餐，他们会不高兴的
They get very upset if you show up late for supper.
- 好吧，那星期日午餐之后  - 好的，再见
- Okay, sunday. No, not before lunchtime.  - Well, ciao.
明天见
See you tomorrow.
再见
Bye.
不，继续
No, go on.
嗯哼，我知道
Uh-huh, I know.
你抓住他的心了，是的，是的，我听得很清楚
You caught one. Yes, yes, I can hear you very well.
你没看到他在害羞吗？
Didn't you see how he was blushing?
他很可爱，但他没有任何…嗯…
He's cute, except he doesn't have any, um...
他从来没有足够的钱缴学校的食宿费
And he never has enough money for room and board at school.
这就是为什么坦娜婊子总是要他做这做那
That's why that bitch Tanner has got him under her thumb.
她给他一堆事情去做
She gives him 1,001 errands to do.
当然
Sure.
我知道了，好的
I got it. Okay.
明天晚上打电话给我，让我考虑一下
Call me back tomorrow evening. Give me a chance to think it over.
是，是，好的，好的
Yes, yes. Okay, okay.
不管怎样，他很可爱
Anyway, he is cute.
可怜的佩特，她很喜欢他
Poor Pat. She liked him a lot.
那可怜的孩子，就这样死了
That poor kid, ending up like that.
我甚至不敢想起这件事
I can't even think about it.
我听说你昨晚有看到她
I heard you saw her yesterday evening.
嗯哼，在学校外面
Uh-huh. Outside the school.
她那时看起来怪怪的
She was acting very strange.
还在喃喃自语
Mumbling to herself.
她被开除时真的感觉很糟，不过这也是她活该
She really felt terrible when they kicked her out, but she really deserved it.
- 那里有很多喧闹声  - 天啊，她很难过
- There was so much noise.  - God, was she difficult.
她说着一些没意义的话
She was saying things that made no sense.
她老是和人争吵、惹麻烦
She was always arguing, causing trouble.
“秘密”
"Secret."
“鸢尾花”
"Iris."
什么？
What?
嗯，我记得…
Uh, I remember...
她提到了“秘密”这个字
She mentioned the word "secret."
然后她…提到了一种花…
And then she...Mentioned a flower...
鸢尾花，我想想，或是丁香花？
Iris, I think, or a lilac.
秘密、花？那是什么意思呢？
Secret flowers? What's that supposed to mean?
我不知道，她是个爱管闲事的人
I don't know. She was a busybody.
她可以轻易从拥挤的人群中找出我们其中一个
It would've been easy for her to find out one of us was in a jam.
- 你觉得欧嘉的家怎么样？ - 很好
- How do you like it at Olga's?  - It's nice.
今早在名单上的八个人跟我到黄色房间来
Those eight on the list this morning, come with me to the yellow room.
- 早安，坦娜小姐  - 苏西
- Good morning, miss Tanner.  - Suzy.
- 早安，布兰克夫人  - 我有好消息要告诉你
- Good morning, madame Blanc.  - I've got good news for you.
- 你的房间已经准备好了  - 喔
- We have it all arranged. Your room is ready for you.  - Huh
这不是很好吗？如果你想要，你今天就可以搬进来
Isn't that marvelous? You can move in today, if you like.
不过如果可以，我想住在欧嘉那里
But I'd rather stay at Olga's, if it's okay.
对我来说没关系，亲爱的
Doesn't matter to me, my dear,
但是在你的入学信函中，你说要住在学校里
But in your letter of enrollment, you said you'd be boarding at the school.
- 我知道，不过…  - 房间现在空出来了
- I know, but...  - The room is free now.
- 我不认为这有那么重要  - 如你所愿吧
- Well, I didn't think it was so important.  - As you wish.
如果你想住在那里，就去住吧
If that's what you want, so be it.
莎拉
Sara?
我不知道你这么固执
I had no idea you were so strong-willed.
我觉得你在做某些决定时太固执了
I see that when you make up your mind about something,
好像没有任何事会改变你
Nothing will change it for you.
我向你致意
My compliments.
女巫！
Witch!
然后在接近十九世纪末的时候
And then, toward the end of the 19th century,
传统芭蕾舞的技巧…
The technique of classical ballet...
采取一种不一样、更有风格性的表现形式
Assumed a different, more stylized impostation.
好吧，让我们热热身
All right. Let's warm up.
怎么了？你不舒服吗？
What's wrong? Don't you feel well?
不，没什么，我只是觉得有一点虚弱
No, it's nothing. I just feel a little weak.
如果情况更糟，我会停止的
If it gets any worse, I'll just stop.
现在来做一些练习
And now some exercises.
丹尼尔，你可以开始了
Daniel, you may begin.
一、二、三、四
One, two, three and four.
一、二…
And one and two...
三、四…
And three and four.
一、二…
And one and two...
三、四…
And three and four.
- 一…  - 抱歉，坦娜小姐
- And one...  - I'm sorry, miss Tanner.
我觉得有一点虚弱，我可以休息一下吗？
I feel a little weak. Can I just rest for a second?
虚弱？拜托，这是很简单的舞步
Weak? Come on. It's an easy step.
这是我们第一次一起练习
This is the first time we've worked together.
我想看看你的能力如何
I want to see what you can do, how far along you are.
现在来和其他同学一起，来吧，我们开始
Now, come along and join the others. Come on; let's go.
丹尼尔
Daniel?
现在大家一起
All together now.
一、二…
And one and two...
三、四…
And three and four.
- 我不行了，拜托  - 一、二…
- I can't. Please.  - And one and two...
三、四
And three and four.
一、二、三、四
And one and two and three and four.
专心点，苏西，把腿抬高一点，你没有瘫痪
Pay attention, Suzy. Get those legs up higher. You're not paralyzed.
把腿抬高一点，一、二、三…
Get those legs up higher. And one and two and three and...
专心点，苏西，一、二…
Pay attention, Suzy. And one and two...
三、四
And three and four.
一、二、三、四
And one and two and three and four.
快走开
Come on. Come on. Run along.
来，喝下去
Come on. Drink up.
- 喔，你…你必须要喝  - 不，够了
- Oh, you...You must drink.  - No, that's enough.
听医生的话
You heard what the doctor said.
- 喝下去  - 不
- Drink up.  - No.
你必须要喝
You must drink.
你出血要吸收液体补充回来
The blood that was hemorrhaging is going back with the intake of liquids.
- 对吧，维迪葛斯教授？ - 没错
- Right, professor Verdegast?  - Obviously.
我亲爱的夫人
My dear madame.
不用担心，没事了，我已经跟年轻的小姐说了
Do not be concerned. It's nothing, as I've already told the young lady.
那我可以放心了，教授，你现在觉得如何呢，亲爱的？
That's a relief, professor. How do you feel, dear?
- 嗯，好多了  - 这个毛病是出在你的练习上
- Uh, better.  - The fault lies with your exercises.
当人久未锻炼时，剧烈运动会使韧带轻微的撕裂
When somebody's been out of practice, violent movement could cause tiny tears in internal ligaments.
这就是导致流血的原因
Thus the hemorrhaging.
你看起来好一点了，你的脸颊已经恢复一点血色了
You look better already. You've even got color back in your cheeks.
- 没错吧？ - 没错，她看起来好多了
- Isn't that right?  - Oh, yes. She looks much better.
- 喔！ - 别动
- Ow!  - Hold still.
这能很快恢复你的健康
This will get you back into shape in no time.
好了，一两天之后你就会恢复得像新的一样
Here we are. Fine, fine. A day or two, you'll be on your feet, as good as new.
- 谁把我的行李拿过来的？ - 欧嘉，她多么体贴啊
- Who brought my bags here?  - Olga. What a dear.
当她听到你病了，她就马上回家帮你把行李拿过来
The minute she heard you were ill, she went right home and brought your things.
喔，她还把你的五十元原封不动的交给我
Oh, and she also left me your $50, and she didn't take a penny of it.
为什么…为什么她要这样做？
Why...Why did she do that?
- 如果我想要，我会…  - 好了，亲爱的
- If I wanted to, I would...  - Well, my dear,
你现在需要的是安静
What you need now is some peace and quiet.
如果再流血，这未必会发生
If the hemorrhaging should start again, which is very improbable,
你可以打电话给我
You can telephone me.
坦娜，她这个星期都要吃没刺激性的食物
And Tanner, she is to eat bland food for about a week.
而且不能让她吃任何水果
And you mustn't let her have any fruit.
- 一小杯的玫瑰红酒呢？ - 可以
- A drop of vin rose?  - Yes.
好的，每餐一杯红酒对恢复很有好处
Good. A glass of red wine with each meal. It works miracles.
这能够帮助血液制造红血球，减少贫血的发生
Clears up anemia and strengthens red corpuscles. It builds the blood.
好好休息，你会被好好照顾的
Rest well. You're in good hands.
苏西，我们是隔壁邻居
Suzy, we're next-door neighbors.
那么，你搬来这里了
So, you moved in here.
是她们把我搬来这里的
Well, they moved me in here.
其实我并不想
I really didn't want to.
你知道的，当我病倒后，欧嘉就跑回去把我的行李拿来…
You know, as soon as I got sick, your pal Olga ran and got my bags...
然后把我赶出她的家
And threw me out of her place.
她一定认为我得了什么可怕的传染病
She must've thought I had something awfully contagious.
但我无法忍受像十岁小孩一样住在寄宿学校
But I can't stand to live in a boarding school like a ten-year-old.
喔，看起来你恢复体力了
Oh, wow. You come back strong.
对，我真的感觉好多了
Yeah, you know, I feel really well.
我是说，就好像没有发生过事情一样，这太不可思议了
I mean, it's almost as if nothing had happened. It's incredible.
- 这都要感谢维迪葛斯教授  - 维迪葛斯？
- And all thanks to professor Verdegast.  - Verdegast?
- 他来看你？ - 对
- He came to look at you?  - Yeah.
请进
Come in.
嗨，帕罗斯
Hi, Pavlos.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你最好留意那个打火机，他很喜欢它
You'd better keep an eye on that lighter. He really likes it.
好的，不过我不觉得他是小偷
Yes, but I don't think he's a thief.
至少你知道
At least you know.
- 你要在这里吃饭吗？ - 对，她们限制我的饮食
- Are you eating up here?  - Yeah, they put me on a restricted diet.
限制饮食还有酒？
And on a restricted diet, they give you wine?
这是维迪葛斯教授的主意，他说这可以帮助我的血液
That's professor Verdegast's idea. Says it'll build up my blood.
铃声，天啊，这表示在吃晚餐之前只剩下十五分钟
The bell. Oh, god. That means it's only 15 minutes till supper.
我最好去换衣服
I'd better change.
- 待会见  - 好的
- Ciao. See you later.  - Okay.
在哪里？在哪里？
Where? Where?
到处都有，整层楼
Everywhere. The whole floor.
真恶心！真让人恶心！
It's disgusting! It's disgusting!
- 它们从哪里来的？ - 我不知道！我们去看看吧！
- Where are they coming from?  - I don't know! Let's go and see!
- 它们从天花板来的  - 在还没解决之前，所有人都下楼
- They're coming from the ceiling.  - In the meantime, everybody downstairs.
不要让任何人上来
Don't let anyone come up.
我很抱歉，真是羞愧，请原谅我
I'm sorry. Truly mortified. Please excuse me.
不过这跟你并没有关系，夫人
But it was nothing to do with you, madame.
当然没有，女孩们，这不是布兰克夫人的错
No, of course not, girls. It was not madame Blanc's fault.
我们透过邮件
We ordered those cases of food by mail...
向我们认为诚实可靠的公司订购食物
From a reliable firm that we thought to be honest.
很显然，它们运到时已经腐烂了
Obviously, It arrived spoiled.
几天之内，就发生了这些事
In a few days' time, you see what happened.
- 喔，这真是可怕  - 对啊，有一只还掉进我的嘴巴
- Oh, it was awful.  - Yes, one got in my mouth.
我想我们还是幸运的，那些虫子只到了顶楼的下一层
I suppose we're fortunate those things only reached the floor below the attic.
- 那其他楼层没有问题吗？ - 对，我们检查过了
- Are the other floors all right?  - Yes. We checked them out.
只有学生寝室的楼层
Just the floor where the students' rooms are.
好吧，我早上会处理消毒的问题
Well, I'll take care of the problem of fumigating in the morning.
问题还没解决之前，今晚我先做一个临时的安排
In the meantime, for tonight, I've thought of a makeshift arrangement.
亲爱的，你可以去看看他们进展如何吗？
Go and see how they're getting along, will you, dear?
男孩们都很体贴的提供协助
The boys have kindly offered to help,
他们和仆人们把练习厅布置成一个大寝室
And they and the servants are turning the practice hall into a dormitory.
如果你们有人选择要外出住宿，我没有任何反对
If some of you choose to find hotel rooms, I'll have no objections.
但是现在已经很晚了，无论如何…
But it's already late, and in any case,
这种不便只有一个晚上而已
The inconvenience will only be for one night.
我们全部都一起睡
We'll all sleep together.
好极了！你还好吗？
Bravo. You all right?
- 是的，谢谢你  - 很好
- Yes, thank you.  - Fine.
- 一切都还好吗？ - 是的，谢谢你
- Is everything all right?  - Yes, thank you.
- 很好  - 你还好吗？
- Good.  - Are you all right?
是的，布兰克夫人，谢谢你
Yes, madame Blanc. Thank you.
- 喔，这样很舒服，就像露营一样  - 很好
- Oh, it's very comfortable. Just like being in camp.  - Good.
你也要跟我们一起睡在这里吗，布兰克夫人？
Are you sleeping here with us, too, Madame Blanc?
当然，就跟坦娜小姐和其他老师一样
Certainly, as are all the other teachers and miss Tanner.
其他老师也住在学校吗？
Do the teachers live here at school?
没有，他们住在城里
No, they live in town.
她们都在晚餐后九点半离开，就像钟表一样
They leave after supper at 9:30, just like clockwork.
现在很晚了，我关掉电灯，你们不会害怕吧？
It's very late. You won't be afraid if I turn out the lights?
- 各位晚安  - 晚安
- Good night, everyone.  - Good night. Good night.
那家伙喜欢你吗？
Is that guy hot for you?
- 也许  - 这真有趣
- Maybe.  - That's funny.
我听过他是…嗯…
I heard he was, uh...
- 当然，我不太喜欢说别人闲话  - 那是个好习惯
- Of course, I'm not much of a gossip.  - That's a good one.
算了吧，你想追他却没有成功
Come on. You tried to get him and didn't make it.
- 你说谎！那不是…  - 为什么你们两个不闭嘴？
- You liar! That's not...  - Why don't you two shut up?
我们有些人想要睡觉
Some of us want to go to sleep.
嘿，莎拉，忘了它吧，这没关系
Hey, Sara. Forget it. It's okay.
苏西，你睡着了吗？
Suzy, are you asleep?
- 你睡着了吗？ - 还没，有什么事吗？
- Were you sleeping?  - No. What's the matter?
你听到那鼾声吗？
You hear that snoring?
听起来怪怪的
It's weird.
听到了吗？
Hear it?
你想这声音是从哪里传来的？
Where do you think it's coming from?
在帘子后面
Behind the sheet.
说谎！
Lies!
什么？
What?
她们对我们说谎
They lied to us.
校长在这里
The directress is here.
那个打鼾的人是她
That's her, the one who's snoring.
她是校长
She's the directress.
- 你怎么知道？ - 我确定是她
- How do you know?  - I'm sure it's her.
去年的一段时间
Last year, for a while,
我住在客房的其中一间
I lived in one of the guest rooms...
在顶楼的下面
Under the top of the stairs.
有一天晚上
One night,
我听到有人很晚进来
I heard someone coming very late in,
躺到我隔壁房间的床上
Getting into bed in the room next to mine.
然后…
And then...
然后我听到这种古怪的打鼾声
Then I heard this weird kind of snoring.
我告诉你，那真的很古怪，我永远都无法忘记
I tell you, it was so weird I never forgot it.
注意听
Listen.
你听到那声音了吗？
You hear that whistle?
确实一模一样
It's exactly the same.
隔天早上，布兰克夫人跟我说…
The next morning, madame Blanc told me...
校长在学校忙到很晚…
That the directress had spent a few hours at the school...
然后睡在我隔壁房里
And had slept in the room next to mine.
你明白吗？
You see?
所以我知道她是校长
So I know she's the directress.
她在这里
She's here.
她在那里
She's there.
就在帘子后面
Right behind that sheet.
我很感激你们能这么快的消毒好
Thank you. I'm grateful you can take care of the fumigating so promptly.
- 早安，布兰克夫人  - 早安，丹尼尔
- Good morning, madame Blanc.  - Good morning, Daniel.
- 现在一切都就序了吗？ - 都清理好了，夫人
- Is everything in order now?  - All cleaned up, madame.
为了确定，我们还检查了其他楼层
Just to be sure, we checked the other floors too.
坦娜小姐，抱歉
Miss Tanner. Excuse me.
校长昨晚有睡在这里吗？
Did the directress sleep here last night?
- 她没有，早安，丹尼尔  - 早安
- No, she didn't. Good morning, Daniel.  - Good morning.
你知道她正在外面旅行，也许两个星期后她会回来看我们
You know she's away on a trip. Maybe she'll pay us a visit two weeks from now.
抱歉，坦娜小姐，我今天早上要上什么课？
Excuse me, miss Tanner, But which class do I attend this morning?
在红色房间的二年级班
The second-year class in the red room.
谢谢你
Thank you.
停止！
Stop!
停止！停止！
Stop! Stop!
够了！已经够了！
Enough. Enough!
- 你知道发生什么事吗？你知道吗？ - 今天是什么日子？
- Do you know what happened? Do you know?  - What day is it?
你那只满是跳蚤、恶心的狗，竟敢咬艾伯特！
Your lousy, disgusting dog has bitten Albert!
它咬掉了一片艾伯特手臂上的肉
He took a piece out of Albert's arm.
- 什么？ - 你们都听到了吗？
- What?  - Did you all hear that?
那只卑鄙的狗想要让孩子残废
That miserable dog tried to mutilate a child.
布兰克夫人必须紧急送艾伯特到第一诊疗中心缝伤口！
Madame Blanc had to rush Albert to a first-aid center to have stitches put in!
- 那是不可能的  - 那我们一起去第一诊疗中心
- That's impossible.  - Let's go to the first-aid center.
就算你看不到血，至少也能听到那个可怜孩子的哭声吧！
Even if you can't see the blood, at least you can hear the poor child's crying.
够了！
That's enough now!
我的狗很忠诚又乖巧，它从来没有伤害过任何人
My dog's a peaceful, faithful animal. He's never hurt anyone.
那个孩子一定有先招惹它！
The boy must have done something to him first!
喔，那可怜的小东西！可怜的小狗！
Oh, the poor little animal! The poor little puppy!
假如我再看到它接近这个学校，我就要它死！
If I ever see him within a mile of this school again, I'll have him put to death!
住口！
Stop it!
我不允许你这样说，你听清楚了吗？
I won't allow such talk, you understand?
你不允许吗？
You won't allow it?
那么你和你的狗滚出去！
Then get out! You and your dog!
- 走吧！ - 你这个婊子！
- Get moving!  - You bitch!
出去！
Out!
我正要出去，我正要出去
I'm going. I'm going.
不过你要明白…
But try to understand that...
我是瞎子，不是聋子
That I'm blind, not deaf.
你明白吗？
Get it? Huh?
不是聋子
Not deaf.
我不是聋子，你明白了吗？
Not deaf. You understand that?
你明白了吗？
You understand?
啊，新鲜的空气！
Ahh, fresh air!
让我离开这个虚伪的行列吧！
Let me out of this gilded parade.
出去！滚出去！滚得好！
Get out! Get out of here! Good riddance!
喔，帕罗斯，我还要吃这种东西多久？
Oh, Pavlos, how much longer do I have to eat like this?
嘿，注意听
Hey, listen.
她们准时走了
There they go, right on schedule.
那些老师，记得吗？
The teachers. Remember?
你能听到吗？她们正要离开
Can you hear them? They're going away.
你听得到吗？
You hear them?
是的
Yes.
我…
I...
我…我不认为她们会想念学校
I...I don't think they'll even miss school.
什么？你说什么？
What? What did you say?
醒醒
Wake up.
我说，对我来说，她们似乎没有出去
I said, it doesn't seem to me that they're going out.
前门在左边
A front door is on the left.
她们的脚步声往右边走，在学校里的某处
Their footsteps are going to the right, somewhere inside the school.
天啊，苏西
Jesus, Suzy.
- 你真是天才  - 嗯…
- You're a genius.  - Mmm.
好极了
Fantastic.
为什么我以前从未注意到呢？
How come I never noticed that before?
苏西，如果她们没有离开，她们会去哪里呢？
Suzy. If they don't leave, Where do they go?
醒醒，苏西
Wake up. Suzy.
快醒醒，苏西！
Come on. Wake up. Suzy!
我好想睡觉
I'm so sleepy.
我不知道为什么，对不起
I don't know why. I'm sorry.
也许…
Maybe...
也许我们能找到她们真正去的地方
Maybe we can find out where they really go.
当然！对了
Of course! Yes.
开始数她们走的脚步声
Begin to count the steps as they go.
这就像寻找线索一样
It's like the search of alietne.
放轻松
Easy.
怎么了？
What is it? Huh?
走吧
Come on.
快点，我们走吧
Come on; let's go home.
是谁？谁在那里？
Who is that? Who's there?
放轻松，孩子
Easy, boy.
怎么了？
What is it?
发生了什么事？
What's happening?
谁在那里？
Who's there?
等等！
Wait!
可怜的丹尼尔，被撕成了碎片，真令人不敢相信
Poor Daniel. Torn to pieces. Incredible.
没错，但你不能太信任狼犬
Oh, yeah, but you can never put too much trust in wolfhounds.
它们很疯狂，我们以前在格施塔德的别墅养过两只
They're crazy. We had two of them once at the villa in Gestaad.
我的天啊，最先是佩特被疯子杀了
My god. First Pat gets murdered by a madman,
而现在丹尼尔又被他的狗咬死了
And now Daniel is killed by his dog.
对啊，也许这地方有不祥的东西
Yeah. Maybe there's a hex on the place.
对，那我们请神父来驱魔好了
Yeah. Let's call in the exorcist and have it purged.
- 怎么了？有什么问题吗？ - 没有，一切都很好
- What is it? Is something wrong?  - No, everything's all right.
是私人的问题吗，亲爱的？
Is it something personal, dear?
不是，不是那样
No, no, it's nothing like that.
坦娜小姐，你介意吗？
Miss Tanner, would you mind?
我想独自和苏西谈几分钟
I'd like a few minutes alone with Suzy.
怎么回事？
Well? What is it?
我只是想跟你谈谈最近发生的一些事情
I just wanted to talk to you about some of the things that have been happening lately.
喔，我知道你对丹尼尔的死感到不安，我们大家都是
Oh, I know you're upset by Daniel's death, as we all have been.
不，不只是那样
No, but it's more than that.
有人知道谁杀了佩特吗？
Does anybody know anything about who killed Pat?
我今天早上跟警察局长谈过话
I spoke with the chief of police just this morning.
他告诉我，他们有一些明确的线索
He told me they had some definite clues.
- 你知道我来的那晚有看到她  - 是的，你告诉过我
- You know that I saw her the night I arrived here.  - Yes, you told me that.
那时她含糊地说一些奇怪无关的话
And that she was mumbling some strange, unrelated words.
你没有告诉过我
No, you didn't tell me that.
因为这没办法合理解释，那是在暴风雨中
Because it was something that didn't make any sense. It was in a thunderstorm.
我没有注意去听清楚
I just didn't pay much attention to it.
我只能清楚地听到两个字…
I only caught two words distinctly:
“秘密”和“鸢尾花”
"Secret" and "Irises."
我不知道这些是什么意思，但我认为也许很重要
I don't know what they mean, but I thought they might be important.
你做得很好
You've done very well. Congratulations.
我也不知道“秘密”或“鸢尾花”是什么意思
I don't know what the words "Secret" or "Irises" mean either.
但我想应该要让警察知道这件事
But I think it's only right we should let the police know about it.
我只是很惊讶你等了两天才说“哈罗”？
I'm only amazed you waited two days before... hello?
- 你真的把事情弄糟了  - 你在说什么？
- You really messed things up.  - What are you talking about?
因为…也许佩特在跟那天晚上
Because... Maybe Pat was talking to...
这栋房子里的某个人说话
Someone just inside the building that night.
我们知道那个人不是我们学校的老师
And we know that someone wasn't one of the teachers.
来吧
Come on.
现在你使某人落到他们调查范围内了
Now you've put them on the hunt for somebody.
这对你来说有什么差别？
What difference does that make to you?
很大的差别
Big difference.
因为我是佩特的朋友
Because I was Pat's friend.
你突然来到的时候，她正告诉我一些事情
She was telling me something When you suddenly showed up.
她被吓坏了，然后跑了
She got scared and she ran away.
那时她几乎陷入歇斯底里
She was in hysterics almost.
然后她就被杀死了
And then she was killed.
记得当你按门铃时的那个声音吗？
Remember that voice when you rang the bell?
跟你说话的就是我
Well, that was me.
我听到一些奇怪、难以置信和荒谬的事情
I heard strange, incredible, absurd things.
佩特写在笔记上好几个月了
Pat was taking notes on them for months.
在她走之前，她把笔记都给了我
And before going away, she gave me all the notes.
我只有跟一个我非常要好的朋友说过
I've only told one person, a very good friend of mine.
法兰克曼德尔，他是来这里参加一个会议
Frank Mandel. He's here for a convention.
今晚我会让你读这些笔记
I'll let you read them tonight.
苏西，醒醒，拜托，醒醒
Suzy, wake up. Please. Wake up.
笔记不见了！有人从我那里偷走了！
The notes are gone! Someone stole them from me!
你明白吗？笔记不见了
You understand? They disappeared.
不要睡着！请帮帮我！
Don't fall asleep! Please help me!
- 醒醒！帮帮我！ - 我不能
- Wake up! Help me!  - I can't.
不能？
Can't?
这是我唯一剩下的东西，因为我放在身边，看
This is the only thing I got left, and that's because I kept it on me. Look.
- 看  - 这是什么？
- Look.  - What is it?
你到底怎么了？你不记得吗？发生什么事？
What's the matter with you? Don't you remember? What's going on?
这是让我们知道老师每晚去哪里的关键
This is the key that'll get us wherever the teachers go every night.
昨晚我坐在你旁边时想出来的办法
I thought it out yesterday evening while I was sitting here next to you.
苏西，你知道女巫吗？
Suzy, do you know anything about witches?
喔，不！拜托！
Oh, no! Please!
不要留下我一个人！
Don't leave me alone!
我一定要逃走！
I must get away!
等等！
Wait!
等等！等等！等等！等等！
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
在找莎拉吗？她不见了
Looking for Sara? She's disappeared.
但这是不可能的，我昨晚还跟她说过话
But that's impossible. I just talked to her last night.
她今天早上离开了，事实上，没有告诉任何人
She left this morning, as a matter of fact, without telling anyone.
只是拿起她的行李就走了，她被听到在大约六点钟时离开
Just packed her bags and left. She was heard leaving about 6:00.
- 你有听到她离开，不是吗？ - 莎拉？喔，是的
- You heard her leave, didn't you?  - Sara? Oh, yes.
我听到大门被关上和她的脚步声离开了大厅
I heard the door close and her footsteps going down the hall.
然后我听到汽车驶离街道的声音，我猜有人在等她吧
And then I heard a car driving off down the street. I guess someone was waiting for her.
- 但这是不可能的  - 如果她不高兴在这里，她可以告诉别人
- But it's impossible.  - If she wasn't happy here, she could've told someone.
为什么要像小偷一样偷偷溜走？
Why sneak off like a thief?
你好，我可以跟法兰克曼德尔说话吗？好的，谢谢你
Hello. May I speak to Frank Mandel, please? Yes, thank you.
你好，我是苏西邦妮
Hello. This is Suzy Bannion.
不，我们没有见过面，我是莎拉的朋友
No, we've never met. I'm a friend of Sara's.
是的，你好，你知道莎拉在哪里吗？
Yes. Hello. Do you happen to know where Sara is?
她今天早上从学校失踪了
Well, she disappeared from school this morning.
是的，似乎她带着所有行李离开了
Yes, it seems she left and took all her luggage.
是的，嗯，听着，我今天可以跟你见个面吗？
Yes. Uh, listen, could I see you sometime today?
嗯，我真的很担心她
Well, I'm really worried about her.
喔，好极了，在哪里呢？
Oh, great. Where?
在会议中心，好的，我会去那里见你
At the convention center. Okay. I'll see you there.
她没有告知任何同学，我已经问过所有人
She didn't inform any of her classmates. I've already asked all of them.
真烦人，我不明白她为什么要这样做
It's very upsetting. I can't understand why she did it.
我是受他们家庭请托的监护人
I'm the one who's held responsible by their families.
我会打电话给她在日内瓦的父亲，或许她已经到那里了
I'll call her father in Geneva. Perhaps she might have gone there.
我已经打电话给莎拉的父亲，他是意大利驻日内瓦的领事
I've already phoned Sara's father. He's the Italian consul in Geneva.
但他今天不在那里，去度周末了
But he wasn't there today. He was away for the weekend.
他们说他星期一会回来，而且他们不知道关于她的任何事情
They said he'd be back by monday, and they don't know anything about her there.
你知道我为什么这么担心吗？
Well, do you understand Why I'm so worried?
我知道，但我们也只能等她父亲回来了
Yes, but before we both get upset, let's wait for the father's return.
也许他们今天早上会合一起离开的
Maybe they got together this morning and went off on their own.
我非常了解她，她是我三年前的病人
I know her quite well. She was a patient of mine three years ago.
- 你知道了吗？ - 我甚至不知道你是精神科医师
- Were you aware of that?  - No. I didn't even know you were a psychiatrist.
她曾经在她母亲过世时精神崩溃过
Well, she had a nervous breakdown after her mother's death,
所以她来接受我的治疗
And she came to me for treatment.
在她病情好转之后，我们仍然是朋友
After she got better again, we remained friends,
但最近她因为一个朋友向她灌输一些思想而感到不安
But lately she was upset about some notions put into her head by a friend of hers.
- 我希望那个人不是你？ - 不是
- Not you, I hope?  - No.
那是一些疯狂的想法
They were kind of wild ideas.
她发现塔姆学院是于…
She had discovered that the Tam academy was founded...
一八九五年由一位希腊移民海莲娜玛蔻斯建立的
In 1895 by a certain Helena Markos, A Greek immigrant,
而当地人认为她是一个女巫
And that the local people believed her to be a witch.
- 我猜你知道这件事了？ - 不，但我有一种奇怪的感觉…
- I guess you knew that?  - No. But I have a strange feeling...
好像有人已经跟我说过这件事，或是类似的事
That somebody already told me about it...Or something similar.
我不记得了
I can't...can't remember.
那真的让莎拉发挥想像力在十九世纪初期…
Well, that really got Sara's imagination going. Earlier in the 19th century,
玛蔻斯女士被数个欧洲国家驱逐出境
The Markos woman had been expelled from several european countries.
她似乎做过一些事，才使得教徒迫害她
She seemed to have something about her which urged religious people to persecute her.
她也写过一些书，我读过其中一本
She also wrote a number of books, and I read that among the initiated,
书名叫做“黑暗女王”
She went by the name "The Black Queen."
在她定居于这里之后，她变成很多街头流言的主角
After she settled down here, she became the subject of a lot of gossip.
虽然如此，她还是设法得到一大笔钱
Nevertheless, she managed to put her hands on a great deal of money,
然后她建立了塔姆学院
And she founded the Tam academy...
起先是教导舞蹈和神秘学的学校
At first a sort of school of dance and occult sciences.
但是没有维持很久，因为在一九〇五年
But that didn't last long, because in 1905,
在她年满一百岁、也是被诅咒的第十年
After being hounded and cursed at for ten years,
玛蔻斯夫人死于一场大火
Madame Markos died in a fire.
那个事件和巫术一样被人们所关注
That's all there is, as far as witchcraft is concerned.
于是学校被她最喜爱的学生接管，神秘学的课程也被完全废除
The school was taken over by her favorite pupil. The study of the occult was abandoned.
不久后这个地方变成一所着名的舞蹈学院
And soon the place became the famous dance academy.
但这跟当一个女巫有什么关系？
But what does it mean to be a witch?
从一个唯物论者和精神科医师的角度来说
Well, as a believer in the material world and a psychiatrist to boot,
我相信现今对魔法和神秘学的信仰的传播…
I'm convinced that the current spread of belief in magic and the occult...
是精神病的一部分
Is part of mental illness.
坏运气不是摔破一面镜子带来的，而是由坏心情带来的
Bad luck isn't brought by broken mirrors, but by broken minds.
抱歉，米辽斯
Excuse me. Milius?
米辽斯教授可以比我更清楚回答你的问题
Professor Milius can answer your question better than I can.
他写过一本叫做“妄想狂或魔法”的书，相信我
He wrote a book called paranoia or magic, and believe me,
那是这个领域的权威着作
It's the final word on the subject.
不好意思，米辽斯，假如你不介意，我想介绍一位我的朋友
Excuse me, Milius. If you don't mind, I'd like you to meet a friend of mine.
- 小姐  - 她对你最喜欢的话题很感兴趣…
- Fraulein.  - She's interested in your favorite subject:
女巫
Witches.
你能跟她说一些神秘事物的事情吗？
Can you tell her something about the mysterious?
那么，我要走了，我有一个约会
Well, I have to go. I have an appointment to keep.
保持联络
Keep me posted, Hmm?
你好，我很抱歉打扰你
Hello. I'm sorry to bother you.
啊，那你想要知道些什么呢？
Ah, so, what would you like to know?
- 你相信有女巫的存在吗？ - 啊
- Do you believe in the existence of witches?  - Ah.
我知道有些女人被称为女巫
I have known some women who are said to be witches.
- 真的吗？ - 我已经研究这个现象很久了
- Really?  - I have studied the phenomenon for a long time.
我的观点是那是同时期精神病学的
I am of the opinion that it is an important appendage...
重要附属物
Of contemporary psychiatry.
你不相信吗，亲爱的？
You're skeptical, my dear.
坦白说，这有点让人难以相信
Well, frankly, it is a little hard to believe.
- 女巫是什么样的人？ - 她们是邪恶、消极和有毁灭性的
- What do witches do?  - They are malefic, negative and destructive.
她们对于神秘学的知识让她们得到极大的能力
Their knowledge of the art of the occult gives them tremendous powers.
她们能改变事物的发展和人的生命，但只会造成危害
They can change the course of events and people's lives, but only to do harm.
- 你不相信我吗？ - 不，我…
- You don't believe me?  - No, I...
她们的目标是累积个人财富
Their goal is to accumulate great personal wealth,
但只能藉由伤害别人来达到
But that can only be achieved by injury to others.
她们能引起痛苦、疾病，甚至是死亡…
They can cause suffering, sickness and even the death...
不管谁，不管任何理由，只要触怒她们
Of those who, for whatever reason, have offended them.
为什么你对神秘学有兴趣呢？
Why do you have all this interest in the occult?
因为有一些朋友跟我谈到女巫
Because some friends spoke to me about witches.
我也看过一些文献资料
I read some stuff.
你听说过“海莲娜玛蔻斯”吗？
Have you ever heard of Helena Markos?
喔，是的，她是一位非常着名的黑暗女王
Oh, yes. She was a very famous black queen.
一位拥有极大邪恶力量的天才女巫
A powerful witch with a tremendous talent for doing evil,
一位真正的魔法夫人
A real mistress of magic.
她居住并死在这个城市，你知道吗？
She lived and died in the city. Did you know that?
知道，那么这里可能有女巫公会吗？
Yes. And might there exist a guild of witches?
正确的说法应该是女巫集会
The correct term would be a coven of witches.
一个女人成为女王，她的魔力就比…
A woman becomes queen of her magic is a hundred times more powerful...
集会里其他人强一百倍，就好像一条蛇
Than the rest of the coven, which is like a serpent.
它的力量取决于领导者，也就是取决于它的头
Its strength rests with its leader... That is, with its head.
一个失去领导者的集会就好像一条无头的眼镜蛇…
A coven deprived of its leader is like a headless cobra:
是无害的
Harmless.
现今的人类怀疑自然的精神力
Skepticism is the natural reaction of people nowadays,
但魔法至今是存在的
But magic is ever present.
换句话说
In other words:
魔法无处不在
Which means that magic is everywhere,
而且遍及全世界，这是个被确认的事实
And all over the world, it's a recognized fact.
一直都是
Always.
玛克？玛克？
Mark? Mark?
抱歉，大家去哪里了？
Excuse me. Where is everybody?
她们全都去剧院看波修瓦芭蕾的首演了
They have all gone to the theater for the opening of the Bolshoi.
- 为什么没有人告诉我这件事？ - 我不知道
- Then why didn't anyone tell me about it?  - I don't know.
坦娜小姐把票发给每个学生
Miss Tanner obtained tickets for everyone.
- 法兰克，我是苏西，莎拉的朋友  - 苏西？你好
- Frank, this is Suzy. Sara's friend?  - Suzy? Hello?
- 我不能…  - 说大声一点，我不能听得很清楚
- I can't...  - Talk louder. I can't hear you very well.
- 有什么事吗？ - 我还没听到莎拉的消息
- Did something happen?  - Well, I haven't heard from Sara,
但有很多奇怪的事情在发生
But a lot of strange things are happening.
我是说，例如当我吃晚餐时，我…
I mean, for example, when I eat at night, I...
哈罗？哈罗，法兰克？
Hello? Hello, Frank?
哈罗？你听到吗？
Hello? Can you hear me?
法兰克？哈罗？
Frank? Hello?
哈罗？哈罗？
Hello? Hello?
哈罗？
Hello?
哈罗，法兰克，你听到吗？
Hello, Frank, can you hear me?
不！
No!
她们根本没有离开学校
They don't leave the school at all.
前门在左边，她们的脚步声往右边走
The front door is on the left. Their footsteps are going to the right.
二、三、四、五、六…
Two, three, four, five, six,
七…
Seven...
只要数出她们的脚步，我就可以找到她们去哪里
I can find out where they're going by counting their footsteps.
二十步
Twenty.
谁在那里？
Who's there?
地毯，这就是为什么脚步声会在这里停止
Carpet. That's why the footsteps stop here.
这是不可能的，应该有其他的路离开这里
It's impossible. There's gotta be another way out of here.
秘密…我在门的后面看到！
The secret... I saw it behind the door!
三朵鸢尾花！转动蓝色的那朵！
Three Irises! Turn the blue one!
秘密…我在门的后面看到！
The secret... I saw it behind the door!
三朵鸢尾花！转动蓝色的那朵！
Three Irises! Turn the blue one!
我告诉过你，我们必须除掉美国女孩那个婊子！
I told you: we must get rid of that bitch of an american girl!
消失…她必须消失！让她消失，明白吗？
Vanish...She must vanish! Make her disappear, understand?
她今晚没有吃也没有喝任何东西
She won't eat or drink anything this evening.
消失…她必须消失！
Vanish...She must vanish!
她必须死！死！死！
She must die, die, die!
海莲娜，给我力量！
Helena, give me power.
生病！生病吧！
Sickness! Sickness!
把她除掉！把麻烦除掉！
Away with her! Away with trouble!
死亡！死亡！死亡！
Death, death, death!
现在死亡向你逼近了！
Now death is coming for you!
你想杀了海莲娜玛蔻斯！
You wanted to kill helena Markos?
我在这儿，美国女孩！我来了！
Im here, american. Im coming!
你现在要和死亡相会了！活生生的死亡！
You're going to meet death now! The living dead!
女巫，女巫
Witch, witch.